bitinstant.com 2013-05-31

# BitInstant - Providing instant transfers for the bitcoin economy - Privacy Policy

  How it works   |   FAQ   |   Fees and Locations   |   API   |   [Blog](http://blog.bitinstant.com/)   |   Security   |   About Us   |    Contact Us

Pay for Your Bitcoins Quickly, Conveniently and Securely

## Privacy Policy

When accessing our Website, BitInstant will learn certain information about you during your visit. How we will handle information we learn about you depends upon what you do when visiting our site.

If you visit our site to read or download information on our pages, we collect and store the following information about you:

1\. The name of the domain from which you access the Internet  
2\. The date and time you access our site  
3\. The Internet address of the website you used to link directly to our site.  
4\. Email address  
5\. Payment provider username   
6\. Destination exchange account name (such as your mtgox username)  
7\. HTTP user agent including operating system and browser version  
8\. Transaction amounts and timestamps

If you identify yourself by sending us an e-mail containing personal information, then the information collected will be solely used to respond to your message.

The information collected is for statistical and record-keeping purposes. In particular, BitInstant may use software programs to create summary statistics and perform other types of analysis used for the purposes of capacity planning, regulatory compliance, identifying system performance issues and monitoring general stability of our service.

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, BitInstant uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.

BitInstant will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us, nor will such information be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without the approval of the user at the time of collection.

We will not disclose information about our users except where required to do so by law. In particular, should we be served with a valid court order or subpoena we will be required to respond - in such cases we will unless prohibited attempt to inform the subject of any such subpoena. We may also be required to give notice to regulatory bodies in the form of SARs (Suspicious Activity Reports) should any user attempt to transfer large amounts of funds in a way that suggests criminal activity is taking place. Any requirement to disclose information to courts, law enforcement or regulatory bodies will override the provisions of this privacy policy and you should not rely upon this policy to shield you in any form if you are engaged in unlawful activity. 

## About BitInstant

BitInstant is a payment processor for various Bitcoin exchanges and other merchants. Customers of these exchanges and other merchants can easily make a payment to them by using BitInstant, that is an agent and payment processor for those exchanges and other merchants. BitInstant receives money for exchanges and other merchants through various payment systems such as [Dwolla, TrustCash, PayPal]. In receiving those funds, BitInstant acts as an agent and payment processor for various exchanges and other merchants, such as [MtGox, ...]. Funds can be available in as little as 15 minutes and are typically available within one hour at the exchange or other merchant selected by the Customer. All payments are processed automatically.

Bitcoin exchanges sell Bitcoin. BitInstant does not sell Bitcion. Instead, BitInstant assists exchanges and other merchants in receiving payment from Customers in the most efficient way known.

All BitInstant transactions are subject to the Customer Terms of Use and Privacy Policy provided on this site  
Please contact support for a copy of our AML and KYC manual
